# Pol Maynard O. Imbing

1299 Garnet st. Batangas Heights Sub, Bolbok, Batangas 09474715155 Uraman2000@gmail.com polimbing.netlify.com



Pol has almost 3 years of professional experience in the IT and business field, specifically on Android Development and Web Development. He is involved in developing and maintaining Android applications. He also has experience Mvp Architecture, Agile Methodology and Git for version control. He is a good team player, always open and eager to give suggestions, hard worker, enthusiastic, achievement oriented, and can work well under pressure.

#### **Education**

Tertiary AMA Computer College

Bolbok, Batangas City

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2013 - 2017

Secondary University of Batangas

Hilltop, Batangas 2009 – 2013

Primary Batangas City East Elementary School

P.Herera St. Batangas

2003 - 2009

### **Technical Skill**

Programming Languages : JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, Html, Css, Python,

PHP, Java, Kotlin, .Net Core, Unity (C#)

Web Libraries & Framework : Styled Component, Styled System, React, Node.js,

Express.js, TypeOrm, Entity Framework, Laravel,

Axios, Bootstrap, Jquery

**Android Libraries &** 

**Framework** 

Retrofit, RxJava, Glide/Picasso

Software : Android Studio, Visual Studio, Photoshop

Database/DBMS:MySQL, Sqlite, SqlOhers:Agile Methodology, Git

## **Professional Experience**

Feb 2021 – Current

#### Accenture Phils, Inc.

**Application Development Analyst** 

- Assign to create custom application in Maximo, create automation scripts and create workflow to complete the business logic of their process.
- Became tech architect as a release manager's assistance for the developer's changes and integrations.

April - May 2020

#### **Gold Bell Financial Service (Singapore)**

Front-end Web Developer

- Develop Front-end application using React.js, Axios and Styled Component, Styled System for custom Design
- Develop / debug web view according to provided design specification. Build reusable component for future use.
- Worked with designer and Project Manager for deployment in the server.

Jul 2019 - Feb 2021

#### Radio Wealth Finance Company, Inc. (Philippines)

**Full Stack Web Developer** 

- Develop Rest API Using Node.Js, TypeOrm, MsSql, Mysql.
- Develop Front-end applications using React.js and Material–UI.
- Develop a PDC monitoring system to monitor all the pdc transactions of all branches of the company.
- Develop api for Policy Portal using DotNet Entity Framework.

Aug 2018 - Nov 2018

#### **Tektos Ecosystems Limited (Philippines)**

**Android Developer** 

- Created a custom UI view component for the app
- Improving and developing app

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

#### Infotouch (Philippines)

**Android Developer** 

- Work with API developer and App Designer to deliver a use friendly app Stock Marketing app for the company's client
- By Using Retrofit and RxJava for Api Integration
- By Using Kotlin language

# **Personal Experience**

May - June 2017

# Thesis - "Basic Skill Set for Kids" Using Unity

 This app helps kids to develop their problem-solving skills, memory skills creativity skills, etc.

November 2016

– March 2017

# Thesis – "Kto12 Grading System" And "Learning app for kids (Android)"

- Developed an Automatic Grading System that calculate the grades automatically like Spread Sheets.
- The Learning app for kids helps kids to describe and pronounce words, letters, animals, flags, and numbers. It also helps kids to learn to spell the animals.

August - October 2016

#### **Markvile Subdivision**

• Developed a subdivision's billing system

August – October 2015

# Thesis – "BSU Document Tracker" And "Batangas Public Market Locator"

- Developed a Document tracker that tracks all document from other offices and lets the student view where the document is, using Android app.
- The Batangas Public market helps people to locate/Search a specific store from the Android app.

May - September 2014

### **Upwork Formly Odesk**

- Developed a Responsive Front End website.
- Convert Psd Design to Website.